<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>6.9.1969</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Doctor Doom</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>187</Height
><Weight
>102</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>O</Blood_type
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Security_level
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Dr. Victor von Doom, Ph.D a.k.a. Doctor Doom is a Latverian politician who serves as the Monarch and Supreme Leader for the Kingdom of Latveria. He was scarred from an accident and wears an iron mask and armor to hide his true face. He is considered one of the most brilliant minds and scientists on the planet Earth. He is also a sorcerer with skills in magic matching the most powerful beings in the Universe, making him a potential candidate for Sorcerer Supreme. He hopes to bring order and betterment to humanity through world conquest. Unequalled in ability, ego, and will power, he has come into conflict with both superhumans and cosmic beings. He is best known as the rival of Reed Richards and archenemy of the Fantastic Four.</Background
><Strengths
>Super-Genius Intelligence: Doctor Doom's most dangerous weapon is his intellect. He is one of the top mortal minds on the planet. Doom even cured Ben Grimm of his Thing form. Doom has constructed hundreds of devices, including a working time machine, devices which can imbue people with powers and many types of robots.His most frequently used robots are his "Doombots," exact mechanical replicas of himself. They look like him, talk like him, and even act like him. Individually, Doombots have an advanced AI (artificial intelligence) so that each one believes itself to be the real Doom. As a safety measure, each Doombot has a dampener program that is triggered whenever the real Doom (or another Doombot) is nearby. These "body doubles" appear when Doom cannot be present or is unwilling to risk his own life, and are often responsible for Doom's seeming return from certain death. Another common type of robot used is the Servo-Guard, the police force of Latveria. Doom specializes in all levels of physics, robotics, cybernetics, genetics, materials science, weapons technology, biochemistry, and time travel. He also has natural talents for leadership, strategy, politics, and manipulation. He has been shown as a prodigious electrical and mechanical engineer, admired by Tony Stark, an inspired theoretician with extensive knowledge of parallel universes and dimensions,[citation needed] and even a practiced neurosurgeon, having surgically separated Hulk from Bruce Banner. His knowledge extents to virtually any scientific field and his mind is said to work as fast as a sophisticated computer.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>It has been shown in the past that Doom can be manipulated by pandering to his sense of superiority, especially over Reed Richards. Spider-Man was able to gain his assistance concerning unknown technology by saying Reed could not figure it out. This ego is also the main reason for his vendetta against Reed, as he cannot accept that Reed understood his equations better than he did. </Weaknesses
></fields>