<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>22.11.1973</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Deadpool</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>1,88</Height
><Weight
>102</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>O negative</Blood_type
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Security_level
><Signature
>Deadpool</Signature
><Date
>22.11.2022</Date
><Employee_code xfdf:original="Employee code"
>T122-05</Employee_code
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Wade Wilson had always been rather mentally unstable. In his adulthood, he found himself wanting to be a hero by joining the military, but they turned him down because of his mental instability. And to make matters worse, Wade then discovered that he was diagnosed with lung cancer and was slowly dying. He broke up with his girlfriend to spare her from the burden of a man doomed to die, however it wasn't long before the Weapon X program came to him, offering not to cure his cancer, but to work around it to make him into the hero he always wanted to be. The program gave him a healing factor that negated his cancer... But also made him even more insane, and massively mutilated his face with rapidly-growing tumors. Because his healing factor made him nearly unkillable, the sadistic Dr. Killebrew used him for his experiments that would kill any normal human being. He escaped the Weapon X facilty and took up the mantle of the hero, Deadpool. Except... Whether or not he's a hero is pretty debatable.</Background
><Strengths
>Regeneration/Healing Factor.
Extended longevity.
Skilled marksman, swordsman, martial artist and hand-to-hand combatant.
Master assassin.
Using devices granting teleportation and holographic disguise.
Fourth wall breaks.
Peak human speed.
Superhuman strength, durability, stamina, reflexes and agility.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Drop a planet on him. Recently, Deadpool canonically died in the Marvel Comics universe. ...
Use Thanos. ...
Remove his 'curse' ...
Turn off his healing factor. ...
Use Carbonadium on him. ...
Complete disintegration. ...
Cure his cancer. ...
Use Loki.</Weaknesses
></fields>