<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>1930</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Stephen Strange</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>1.8</Height
><Weight
>81</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>B+</Blood_type
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Security_level
><Signature
>Stephen Strange</Signature
><Date
>24.08-22</Date
><Employee_code xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT22-09</Employee_code
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Doctor Stephen Vincent Strange, M.D., Ph.D is a Master of the Mystic Arts. Originally being a brilliant but arrogant neurosurgeon, Strange got into a car accident which resulted with his hands becoming crippled. Once Western medicine failed him, Strange embarked on a journey to Kamar-Taj, where he was trained by the Ancient One in the ways of Magic and the Multiverse. Although he focused on healing his hands, Strange was drawn into a conflict with Kaecilius and the Zealots, who were working for Dormammu and had sought to merge Earth with the Dark Dimension to find an eternal life. Following the demise of the Ancient One and the defeat of Kaecilius, Strange then became the new protector for the Sanctum Sanctorum, seeking to defend the Earth from other inter-dimensional threats.</Background
><Strengths
>Magic: As the master of the New York Sanctum and a former candidate for the position of Sorcerer Supreme,[16] Doctor Strange possesses an extremely high level of mastery over magic which he used to defend his native reality. With the death of the Ancient One, Doctor Strange is currently the most powerful member of the Masters of the Mystic Arts. Indeed, despite his initial inexperience, an impressed Karl Mordo and Wong claimed that Strange's prodigious skills meant that he was "born for the mystic arts," and the Ancient One herself noted that Strange has tremendous potential as a sorcerer. Indeed, even while still inexperienced, Strange was able to use the powers of the Time Stone's container, the Eye of Agamotto, quite effectively and safely, despite it being considered to be very dangerous for the natural order. With the help of numerous mystical artifacts and relics, in addition to his astral powers, Strange is able to gain access to a multitude of mystical powers. Strange makes up for his lack of experience with his gifted intellect, photographic memory, and ingenuity, as he swiftly imprisoned Loki, an extremely skilled master of Asgardian Sorcery, and even defeated Kaecilius by outsmarting Dormammu, forcing the latter to leave Earth's dimension and take Kaecilius with him. Strange was predicted by Zola's algorithm to become a significant enough potential threat to HYDRA to be targeted by Project Insight. By the time of the Infinity War, Strange dramatically improved his power and skill in magic as he received more training and gained more experience. He proved capable of single-handedly combating Thanos' use of the Infinity Gauntlet more effectively than the Guardians of the Galaxy and even Iron Man, with even the Titan himself praising Strange for his use of the Mystic Arts. The Ancient One stated long before Doctor Strange became a Master of the Mystic Arts that he was always meant to be the best of them. Later on, Doctor Strange was able to grow his power to such a level that he was able to contend against the likes of Scarlet Witch, despite her superior innate power. After tapping into the power of the Darkhold and accessing his third eye, Strange's magic has been increased to unknown levels.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Mortal</Weaknesses
></fields>