<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>14.10.1953</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Thanos</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>201</Height
><Weight
>448</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>unspecified</Blood_type
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Security_level
><Signature
>Thanuse</Signature
><Date
>03.10.22</Date
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Thanos was born on Saturn's moon Titan as the son of Eternals A'lars and Sui-San, the nephew of Zuras, and the grandnephew of Uranos. His brother is Eros of Titan. Thanos carries the Deviants gene, and as such, shares the physical appearance of the Eternals' cousin race. Shocked by his appearance and the belief that he would destroy all life in the universe, Sui-San went insane and attempted to kill him, but she was stopped by A'lars. During his school years, Thanos was a pacifist and would only play with his brother Eros and pets. By adolescence, Thanos had become fascinated with nihilism and entropy, worshipping and eventually falling in love with the physical embodiment of Mistress Death. As an adult, Thanos augmented his physical strength and powers through his superior scientific knowledge using a combination of mysticism and cybernetic enhancements. He also attempted to create a new life for himself by siring many children as well as becoming a pirate. He finds no fulfillment in either until he is visited again by Mistress Death, for whom he murders his offspring and his pirate captain.</Background
><Strengths
>- Thanos is Immortal (and a very old being) and is impossible to kill.- Thanos possesses Superhuman Durability: It is proven by the fact that he can touch and wield the Infinity Stones without getting injured.- His sword is made of the metal Uru, one of the strongest metals in the Marvel Universe.- Comic Thanos is the smartest and the strongest character other than the Gods in the universe. Even without the stones, Avengers combined can beat him only because he subconsciously beats himself.- has the infinity gauntlet</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>- his single most terrible weakness to be: his pride</Weaknesses
></fields>