<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>03.1964</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Scarlet Witch</Name
><Sex
>F</Sex
><Height
>5,7" in</Height
><Weight
>132 lbs</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>0-</Blood_type
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Security_level
><Signature
>Scarlet Witch</Signature
><Date
>24.8.2022</Date
><Employee_code xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT22-03</Employee_code
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Although much of the Scarlet Witch's true origins remain elusive to her thanks tomanipulations by others, she can still recall her early days as a child with her twin brotherPietro. The two lived on Wundagore Mountain in Eastern Europe, believing themselves bornas mutants to a Romani couple named the Maximoffs. Given the name Wanda, she lived for ashort time in childish innocence until local troubles involving her parents separated her and herbrother from them and forced her to hide her growing powers.</Background
><Strengths
>The source of Wanda's unnatural abilities stem from a two-fold base; unparalleled mastery ofactual magic and an innate power to warp reality.Due to exposure to mystic energies and forces at an early age, Wanda may reshape reality tovarious extremes. Known as a "hex" in her formative years as an Avenger, the Scarlet Witchbelieved she used the ability to affect probabilities for a positive benefit to herself, though attimes to imprecise outcomes. Later, she mastered the ability and began to understand it as aliteral altering of reality.In addition, Wanda trained under other magicians and spellcasters to become proficient inmagic-use, which manifests from incantations and spells. To this end, she has become one ofthe most proficient sorceresses on Earth.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Though she does not possess a quite-so specific rogues gallery as many of her fellow costumechampions, the Scarlet Witch can claim a few immediate enemies from her years with the Avenand her own personal trials.The powerful mutant known as Magneto subverted Wanda at an early age to not only believe h rself tobe a mutant, but also his daughter. Wanda eventually rebelled against the villain's manipulation toultimately confront him whenever encountered and act as a bulwark to his schemes. Doctor Doanother dominant personality in Wanda's life, desired her powers for himself, and betrayed her henshe sought him out once to help her uncover missing memories. Later, Doom closeted her in his nativecountry after a dramatic event, taking advantage of the amnesia she then suffered under andproclaiming his supposed affections for her.The enetic enius called the Hi h Evolutiona has also caused miser in the Scarlet Witch's Iiclaiming responsibility for her abilities and confusing her further as to her and her brother's parentage.</Weaknesses
></fields>