<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>10.10.1968</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Vision</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>1.91</Height
><Weight
>136.08</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>V</Blood_type
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Security_level
><Signature
>Vision</Signature
><Date
>24.08.2022</Date
><Employee_code xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT22-10</Employee_code
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>The metal monstrosity called Ultron, constructed by the size-changing scientist Henry Pym himself, inadvertently gained sentience and rebelled against the Avengers' resident roboticist. After six months of failure, Ultron kidnapped the first Human Torch's initial creator, Professor Phineas T. Horton. Ultron decided to create his own android using the android Human Torch of the 1940s (actually a divergent Human Torch created by Immortus for his own machinations) to serve as a vehicle of vengeance against the Avengers. Ultron had Professor Horton color the android's face red, and also had Professor Horton alter the Horton Cells of which the Torch consisted, giving his creation density-shifting powers. When the Vision was "birthed," however, Ultron discovered that Professor Horton had not erased or destroyed the Vision's memories as the Torch. Ultron killed Professor Horton for having betrayed him, and the "Torch" sought vengeance. Ultron defeated him and endowed the Vision's neural processors with the brain patterns of Simon Williams, the ionically charged costumed champion called Wonder Man, implanting a control crystal to keep him in check.</Background
><Strengths
>The Vision possesses a number of superhuman powers ultimately derived from his artificial substance and metabolism. The Vision's android body is a functioning replica of a human body containing analogues to virtually all human organs, blood, and tissue, composed of an unrevealed synthetic organic-like substance, presumably Horton Cells. This substance mimics all the functions of human tissue, but is several times as strong, durable and resilient.[citation needed] Computer Brain: The Vision's brain functions like a computer enabling him to interact, wirelessly or directly, with other computer systems to utilize or extract data from them which can be stored in his databanks. He has used these abilities to disable the Avengers' security systems and gain direct control of the world's nuclear weapons systems. He is also able to receive transmissions from other computers if he establishes and maintains a connection with the Avengers' computers in their base of operations.[citation needed]     Superhuman Intelligence: He has a vast amount of information (possibly a library's worth) stored in his computer brain which he can refer to at any time, and he is also capable of rapid analysis of huge amounts of data.[citation needed]    Nanite Body: After his 'Ultron Imperative' protocol became active, the Vision spent hours absorbing solar energy and gathering raw materials to re-create his body so that it would be made entirely out of nanobots. This enabled him to disassemble into a stream of millions of nanites, enabling it to fit into and travel through extremely small spaces. Each nanite carries a copy of the Vision's A.I. programming, possibly enabling him to scatter and reconstruct a brand new body from a single unit. It also allows him to capitalize on his natural cyberpathic and technopathic manipulation capabilities by disassembling and infiltrating systems, rewiring them from the inside out via his near atomic scale semblance.[citation needed] </Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Rigidity: The Vision is capable of increasing his density past the point where his muscles can exert enough power to move his body. Over a certain threshold, it becomes more and more difficult for the Vision to move his exceedingly massive frame. At his maximum density of 90 tons, the Vision becomes a literally immovable object and is effectively immobilized in place until he chooses to reduce his density back to a more comfortable level.[citation needed] In the past, the Vision's pursuit of being "human" would temporarily deter him.[citation needed] Somehow, the Vision, though he has a mechanical brain, was once successfully drugged with the same knockout drug that also took out Hawkeye, the Black Panther, and the Black Knight</Weaknesses
></fields>