<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>01.04.1964</Date_of_birth
><Name
>Daredevil</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>1,83</Height
><Weight
>79</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>B-</Blood_type
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Security_level
><Signature
>Daredevil</Signature
><Date
>25.8.2022</Date
><Employee_code xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT22-17</Employee_code
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>Daredevil's origins stem from a childhood car accident that gave him special abilities. While growing up in thehistorically gritty or crime-ridden working class Irish-American neighborhood of Hell's Kitchen in New York City,Matt Murdock is blinded by a radioactive substance that falls from an out-of-control truck after he pushes a manout of the path of the oncoming vehicle. While he can no longer see, his exposure to the radioactive materialheightens his remaining senses beyond normal human ability, and gives him a "radar sense." His father, a boxernamed Jack Murdock, is a single man raising his now blind son, who despite his rough upbringing, unconditionallyloves his son and tries to teach him to form a better life for himself. Jack is later killed by gangsters after refusing tothrow a fight, leaving Matt an orphan. In order to protect himself, Matt began training to hone his physical abilitiesand superhuman senses under the tutelage of a mysterious blind stranger named Stick, eventually becoming ahighly skilled and expert martial artist.Some years later, after graduating from law school with high grades, Matt seeks out the criminal element in Hell'sKitchen and starts his crime-fighting activities. Matt targets the local gangsters who murdered his father andsucceeds in bringing them to justice. Eventually, donning a costumed attire modeled after a devil, Matt took up aretending to have a sighted identical twin brother named Mike Murdock, who Matt would claim was Daredevilwhenever his identity was made public knowledge, and occasionally impersonate, Mike is brought into existencefollowing an encounter with a reality-warping mutant, before cementing his existence alongside Matt in history witha magic spell.</Background
><Strengths
>Superhuman agility, reflexes, senses, and balance.Blindsight.High pain tolerance.Mastery of stick-fighting, martial arts, and acrobatics.Utilizing billy club with multi-purpose functions.Expertise in criminology. </Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Inlove with his best frend</Weaknesses
></fields>