<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xfdf="http://ns.adobe.com/xfdf-transition/"
><Date_of_birth xfdf:original="Date of birth"
>01.02.1974</Date_of_birth
><Name
>The Punisher</Name
><Sex
>M</Sex
><Height
>1,85</Height
><Weight
>95</Weight
><Blood_type xfdf:original="Blood type"
>B</Blood_type
><Rank
>Junior Data Analyst</Rank
><Security_level xfdf:original="Security level"
>C</Security_level
><Signature
>The Punisher</Signature
><Date
>24.8.2022</Date
><Employee_code xfdf:original="Employee code"
>IT22-04</Employee_code
><Department
>Medical Data Department</Department
><Background
>The Punisher (Francis "Frank" Castle, born Castiglione) is a fictional antihero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. The character was created by writer Gerry Conway and artists John Romita Sr. and Ross Andru. The Punisher made his first appearance in The Amazing Spider-Man #129 (cover-dated February 1974), originally depicted as an assassin and adversary of Spider-Man.The character is depicted as an Italian-American[9][10] vigilante who employs murder, kidnapping, extortion, coercion, threats of violence, and torture in his campaign against crime. Driven by the deaths of his wife and two children, who were killed by the mob for witnessing a killing in New York City's Central Park, the Punisher wages a one-man war on crime.[11] A veteran (originally of the Vietnam War[12][8] and later updated alternately to the fictional Siancong War and the Iraq War)[13][14] U.S. Marine Corps Scout/Sniper in Force Recon, Castle is skilled in hand-to-hand combat, guerrilla warfare, and marksmanship.[9][10] He is well known by his skull motif on his chest, originally envisioned by his creators as a skull-and-crossbones symbol on his right breast</Background
><Strengths
>The Punisher is the recipient of intense infantry training from the United States Marine Corps and special operations training by Force Recon. As a Recon Marine he went through Airborne School, Ranger School, BUDs,[84] the Q-Course, and SERE; as well as cross-training with the Australian SASR during the Vietnam War. From this training, the Punisher is proficient in not only basic infantry and special operations skills, but the use and maintenance of specialized firearms, equipment, and explosive ordnance. He is highly trained in infiltration into heavily guarded enemy territories and structures for the purpose of assassination, capture, and military intelligence. As a Scout/Sniper he is highly trained in various forms of camouflage and stealth in different environments. He is also highly proficient at hand-to-hand combat, and has been trained in multiple forms of martial arts such as Chin Na,[37] Hwa Rang Do,[37] Krav Maga,[85] Muay Thai,[85] Nash Ryu Jujutsu,[37] Ninjutsu, Shōrin-ryū Karate[37] and Systema.[85] Both Nick Fury and Tony Stark have commented on how extraordinarily high his pain tolerance is.[citation needed] He refuses to take painkillers, as he feels that their benefit of dulling pain is not worth the side effects of drowsiness and slowed reflexes.</Strengths
><Weaknesses
>Due to the Punisher's homicidal nature, few of his foes became recurring antagonists, the most notable of these being the severely-scarred enforcer Jigsaw and the brutal sadistic mercenary Barracuda. The Punisher also acquired a nemesis in the form of the Kingpin,[33] a longtime Spider-Man and Daredevil foe, and developed enmity with Daredevil himself, who likewise abhorred and fought against the Punisher's brutal methods. Villains such as the Jackal, Bushwacker, Doctor Doom,[34] The Reavers and Bullseye would be used to provide more of a challenge for the character. In addition, heroes such as Spider-Man, Captain America, Daredevil, Ghost Rider,[35] the Hulk, Wolverine,[36] Nick Fury, and Moon Knight[37] – and, on at least two occasions, the preadolescent team Power Pack[38] – would appear. Often the stories would use the appearance of those heroes to provide commentary on the difference between the Punisher and those more colourful characters. During Don Daley's run on The Punisher title, his version of justice was described by the editor as "an eye for an eye".[</Weaknesses
></fields>